Aslam Khalil

Front End Developer

Solution-driven Developer adept at contributing to a highly collaborative work environment, finding solutions and determining customer satisfaction. Demonstrated talent for quick learning and adaptability with 2 years of experience in HTML, CSS, Javascript and React.

EXPERIENCE

RobotICT, Prague — *Full-Stack Developer*

September 2021 - December 2021

- Refactored all data tables and templates in the company's software product (DNA) for better UX.
- Designed and updated layouts to meet usability and performance requirements using Meteor.js.
- Collaborated with senior developers in an Agile Scrum environment to effectively maintain project timelines and utilize available resources.
- Contributed in the development cycle of the DNA project by learning its functionality and suggesting better approaches to enhance its performance.

Risidio, London — *Front-End Developer*

February 2022 - Present

- Collaborating with indigionous artists to generate NFTs on the Risdio marketplace. https://staging.risidio.com/
- Implementing new designs made by the design team on Risidio corporate website. https://risidio.com/
- Optimizing and refactoring the code for various web applications for enhanced performance and usability.
- Fixing and improving old code to be clearer and readable for current and future developers.

Portfolio, https://my-portfolio-85947.web.app/

442 Sandy Hill Road Farnham/Surrey +44 7305 172995

aslamhanikhalil@gmail.com

SKILLS

- HTML
- CSS
- Javascript
- React/Vue
- MongoDB
- Meteor
- MaterialUI/Bootstrap
- Git/GitHub/GitLab
- Scrum/Trello

EDUCATION

Udemy/FreeCodeCamp/Stackov erflow

February 2020 - September 2021

Level 4 in European Digital Marketing & Entrepreneurship

August 2021 - December 2021

BA in Modern Languages and Literature

Najah National University July 2015 - December 2018

LANGUAGES

English, Arabic, Hebrew, Urdu

HOBBIES

Outdoors: Skiing/Diving/Hiking Sports: Football/Basketball

Reading: Literature/Philosophy/Travel